Hi everyone! It's a new video here on my channel and I'm wearing a bodysuit from Bright and Shiny
because normally we know Bright and Shiny for their superior latex outfits. We all remember
that one made to measure catsuit for example. Right, but today it's not about latex because
maybe you don't notice but Bright and Shiny also offers spandex items. So today I'm going to show
you some of these. Here we go let's start with the first one. The first item is a black catsuit
because I just love black catsuits and I love to have a basic black catsuit in every material so
to say. So this is going to be my favorite basic spandex catsuit from now on because I mean look
at the fit. It's so good and it's so comfy. The fabric is made in Italy. It's really high quality
and normally it's used to make sportswear outfits and supposedly it gets even softer
after you wash it for the first time. I have to confess I did not wash it yet. I tried it on for
a quick test and to do some reels and I can tell that it's already really soft so I'm looking
forward to washing it and getting it even softer. I have a front zipper here and also stirrups on
hands and feet. You can totally customize your suit. You can add gloves. I will show you a suit
with gloves later on by the way. You can add a hood, cutouts for mouth or eyes. You can add socks
or even stirrups or nothing at all for example. So check out the Bright and Shiny webshop and
have a look at all the various customization options. To show you some of said customization
options I'm going to switch into the next outfit. Alright the red suit and you
can see it's slightly see-through I'm wearing a black bra underneath but I
think the color is really cool kind of wet look shine also it almost looks a
bit metallic like a metallic effect I don't know if you can tell but I think
it's really cool haven't seen it like this before I have gloves here I have socks in this suit
so really full body there's also a hood without any cutouts so it's basically so tight and you
can make the order made to measure so if you're not on friendly terms with off the rack sizes
go for it and get one made to measure I can definitely recommend this so it's going to be
a really great fit as always I choose my catsuits with a crotch zip because it's more
handy or handier that way you can also see here a zipper I don't know if you notice but it's the
exact same color as the fabric which is really cool these are YKK zippers so they're available
in a crazy color range a lot of colors and it's just a match with every bright and shiny
spandex color which is really cool I do have two leggings in two other colors and I'm going to show
them to you as well I pink leggings and I paired it with a black dress and black heels because
it makes the pink really stand out and even brighter
I think all in all it's a pretty cool look I did not expect this to be honest
and I have stirrups here again what I love about stirrups is that it keeps the leg and the leggings
in place and the fabric is not able to ride off my leg and look too short so that's a big
thumbs up for me for stirrups on legs and all on arms too
We have a normal waistband here but there are other options available.
Again I can only say check out the webshop.
And for the last item some tights in purple.
Last item are these tights.
They are really nice purple, like a cool purple and I got my light close to me so you can
see the shine even better because I think it's awesome.
I really like this one.
Also think sitting and these heels and shiny tights together are just really really nice.
Anyway, I hope you enjoyed this video.
Thanks to Bright and Shiny for sending these spandex items along. I really enjoyed them.
I really love the catsuits and
And yeah, thanks to every one of you for watching this video.
Check out my channel, check out my other pages, check out Bright and Shiny.
I will link everything in the description text below this video.
Don't forget to hit thumbs up and subscribe to my channel.
And I will see you in the next video. Have a nice one. Bye.